Hello. My name is Ebuki Mita from Clancop. Pleased to meet you.
Yes, I am. I'm in the room of Breathless,
I'm very nervous today,
My cheek muscles are already twitching,
My head was half blank, wondering what to do,
But today, we are going to proceed,
I don't know if I'll be able to do it very, very well, but I'll do my best,
I don't know if I can do it very well, but I will do my best. I am not sure if I will be able to do it very well, but I will do my best.
I'm not sure if I can do it very, very well, but I'll do my best. So I would like to call today's guest.
Today's guest is this person.
Good afternoon.
Please come in.
Oh, wait a minute.
Exquisite pause.
Then, please introduce yourself.
Yes, I'm Kanako Momota.
I'm Anna from the countryside in Ekberguin, the Mamelokrone version and Kanako Momota.
Pleased to meet you.
Please do.
Well, what a pleasure.
No, it's nice to meet you both.
We often get together, you know, in folk villages and stuff,
Yes, that's right. So it's been about a month since we last met,
It's still a little bit...
Do you usually facilitate in the group?
Do you have a specific role?
Not at all,
Is that right?
That's right. I do a lot of the day-to-day facilitation, but it varies,
Daily? Who is it today?
Yes, that's right.
That's great.
Yes, that's great. So today I get to talk with Kanako,
I'd like to talk about various things,
Please feel free to ask me anything.
First of all, let me tell you about Kanako-chan,
Kanako-chan was born on July 12,
Kanako was born on July 12 and I was born on July 19,
We have the same month of July in common,
That's right.
Last year, I received a phone call from Kanako-chan,
Yes! Yes!
That's right. Yes, I did.
You were walking, right?
Yes, I was. I was just going to rehearsal,
I was trying to catch a cab.
That's right.
Kanako called me,
I was so happy,
I was desperate to catch a cab,
Cab! I kept saying things like, "Taxi!
I felt really bad about that.
It wasn't like that at all.
It was just that I said it at a very strange time.
I was happy.I was so happy.
Soon it will be our birthday.
It's not too soon. It's already on,
Today. When it's on-air,
Yesterday, tomorrow, my birthday.
Did you say the 11th or the 12th?
That's right.
Already.
Happy birthday to you.
Happy birthday to both of us.
I'm so happy for you.
How old will you be next?
I'm turning 23.
Twenty-three.
That reminds me. I remember my 23 years old.
But it was just around the time of Mr. Momoguro's 10th anniversary.
I'm 29 years old now, right?
Eight, seven, six, five, four,
About before the 10th anniversary?
I think I'm just about to celebrate my 10th anniversary.
That's fast.
It all happened so fast.
It all happened in the blink of an eye.
That's why I think it's really amazing.
When I think about when I will be 23 years old,
I think that when I will be 23 years old, you will be singing on a big stage at that age.
No, no, no, but, you know, you have to work every day, don't you? I mean, you have a lot of work every day, don't you?
I think it's really great that you are working so hard.
This is my line.
We are praising each other.
But, I have one thing that really impressed me,
There was one thing that really impressed me,
Impressive?
Yes.
I saw an interview with Kanako-chan? I saw an interview with Kanako?
I saw an interview with Kanako where she said that she used to have a complex about her voice,
I think my voice is the complete opposite of Kanako-chan's, but I really sympathize with her,
I think I have the exact opposite type of voice to Kanako, but I felt like I could really relate to her,
Really? Really? I heard she has such a wonderful voice.
Kanako-chan wrote that she couldn't sing cool songs at that time,
I, on the other hand, can't sing idol-like songs even though I'm an idol,
I can't sing idol-like songs, or cute songs, in the opposite sense,
I also have a history of hitting my mother,
I can really relate to it.
So you felt it was difficult to sing idol-like songs because of your voice?
And when I sang in a group, I had a hard time singing songs that sounded like idols because of my voice,
I was able to change my character and my voice.
You would stand out in a group where the other members are all together,
Yes, that's right.
Is it because of the difference in the quality of your voice?
Yes, it is.
That's a good thing,
I don't think I have such a weapon.
That is your weapon,
It's true that now I have people telling me that they like my voice,I certainly have people tell me now that they like my voice now, too,
In the past, as you know, Mida-chan, that's exactly what I used to do,
But now, I think I'm fundamentally tone-deaf, or rather, I can't sing.
I was just really bad at singing.
I was really just a bad singer,
I blamed it on the quality of my voice,
No matter what I sang, I couldn't make it look good. I felt that no matter what I sang, it wouldn't be cool, and I couldn't decide what to sing,
I thought it was because I have this voice,
I was just making up reasons and excuses,
But now I think it is my weapon,
But now I feel that they are my weapons and charm points,
But I also feel that they are my weapons now, and there are many things that I consider to be my charm points,
I've had a lot of people who love Mita-chan's voice,
There are many people who love Mita-chan's voice,
There are a lot of people who want to hear that, don't you think?
I was also saved by those people,
I feel like I was saved by those people, or rather, I feel like I was saved by those people who turned my complex into a charm point.
It's amazing.
But I really like it. I also like Tanaka's song.
It really sticks with me. It sticks directly to me.
Even now, of course, there are many things I'm not good at,
I wonder why I can't do them. I still have to ask myself, "Why can't I do all these things?
But the moment someone says something like that to me, it saves my life and makes me feel glad that I am doing what I do.
That's why you performed "White Wind" at the Staples Festival, didn't you?
No, no, I thought it was really great at the time.
It was because I had been listening to Kanako's "White Wind" for a long time,
Even my voice trainer said to me, "You are not Kanako,
I really didn't know how to make it my own,
I was really on the edge of my seat, trying to figure out what to do,
And all the kids from STAPLA were on the perimeter, with Mokuro and the other members around me,
I was really nervous to sing the chorus by myself in the midst of all the other members of the group,
The first time I sang the chorus of "Noro no ochi-chabi" (When I became Cinderella),
When I sang the chorus of Shirano, it was when I became Cinderella.
At that time, it wasn't so much that I was going to be Cinderella, but rather that I was looking forward to everyone watching me sing the chorus,
I was more excited to be seen by everyone,
I was excited to be able to sing,
I was thinking that I had to sing so as not to destroy Kanako's important parts,
I was impressed again when I sang "White Wind",
But that part is really difficult, isn't it?
It's true that when I sing it myself, I wish I could do it better,
There are many things I wish I could do better,
But now that Sanda-chan sang my part, I realized how I can make it my own,
I wondered how I could make it my own,
I have experienced many such struggles,
I know exactly how you feel,
I know how it feels to be under such pressure,
I don't like it. I don't like it. I don't like it.
But I was able to make it really Eve's own,
I was thinking, "How can I make it my own?
I started from a place of thinking about how to make it mine,
It all belonged to eveve,
And the result is something that only eveveve can do,
I can't do that,
I could never produce something like that,
That's why I was so happy that she sang "White Wind" with so much passion.
Now let's sing together.This time together.
Chisato vs. the Demon Doctor.
Chisei, by all means.
Are you okay?
I'm fine. I'm sure of it.
It's like I'm going to fail in this.
No, no, no.
I couldn't sing well at all.
But that's the beauty of a live performance,
It was something that could only be achieved at that time,
Whether I failed or succeeded,
Because whether you failed or succeeded, you were really challenging yourself,
I'm sure you were giving it everything you had at that moment,
I think that's really wonderful.
I'm glad to hear that. Thank you.
I feel encouraged again.
I think we have something else in common,
We are both probably Indian,
I'm also very much an Indian person,
I was wondering what you do when you are not working at home,
I was wondering what you do when you are not working at home. I don't do anything.
Me neither.
Really?
I often say that I'm doing nothing,
That's how I feel.
But I watch movies and dramas,
I watch movies and dramas like this.
I see.
I watch them like this, and when I feel hungry, I eat a meal and watch the rest of the movie,
I eat dinner and watch the rest of the movie,
And when I think it's nighttime, I eat dinner again,
And then I eat again, and then I relax.
Then I go in and watch again,
I end up staying up late and going to bed.
Me too. I'm not really doing anything.
It would be like saying that I don't really do anything,
I guess I just go to the movies or something.
I think I only go to about three places.
Even the people at home.
But I understand.
You're sitting on the couch and your butt starts to hurt, and then you finally realize it.
What's that? I've been here for quite a while.
On the other hand, it is harder to stand up.
If you stay in the same position for a long time.
That's true.
But usually I am with the members,
I was with the staff,
But usually you spend most of your time with other people, with the members, with the staff, and so on.
That's why I like to spend time alone,
I like that kind of thing very much,
I think that's probably true.
Yes, that's true. I love my alone time.
I don't know if I can say I love it.
I like both,
So I go to movies and karaoke all by myself.
That's great.That's great.
You also go to karaoke.
I also go to karaoke by myself.
That's exactly what I did at the Staples Festival,
Or when I was invited to run at the White Wind Festival,
He stayed in the karaoke room all the time,
He practiced at karaoke.
That's right.
I am the type of person who does not like to be seen working hard,
I don't want the members to see it either,
When I was given such an important role,
I am the type of person who cannot practice in the dressing room.
So, I prefer to practice in a place where I can be alone,
But if I go home, my family will hear me,
So I stay in my karaoke room.
I see. So you are a karaoke singer.
That's right.
So you feel like that.
It's a different environment from the one in which you concentrate,
So you go to karaoke,
It's YASUKE-san, isn't it?
I'm glad. I'm really happy.
I said it myself.
But you really like it.
But do you go shopping with your sister?
Or do I go shopping alone?
And the Internet.
Your sister.
That's right.
I don't really make plans with my friends to go somewhere.
I like it, but I'm still concerned about it,
I like it, but I'm still concerned about my schedule,
It's hard to know when our work is going to open,
I don't know when our work is going to open,
I don't know when our work is going to open, so I don't want to contact her suddenly,
I think about it a lot,
I think it would be better to go alone.
I understand.
That's how I feel.
Family is one thing.
Well, then, be close to your family,
What?
Yes, that's right.
It saves you. In many ways.
Yes, it is.
I love Disney,
Whenever I go to Disney, it's always with my family,
I always go to Disney with my family or my sister.
That's why my sister takes most of the pictures I put on Instagram.
I know what you mean. I know what you mean.
My sister takes most of the pictures.
At first, I tend to take pictures of my mom,
I would tell her the angle and stuff like that.
I ask her to take another shot.Have them take one more picture.
You can say that without worrying.
That's right.
And the mothers and so on,
I don't know if they are of my generation or not,
I don't know if it's their generation, but when I ask them to take a picture, they only take one picture.
Yes, yes, yes.
That's right.
I just snapped a picture and got it.
And it was taken at an angle.
I was like, "What kind of angle am I shooting from? It's almost like a view,
I understand.
But you are getting better at it little by little.
But in that aspect, you know,
I mean, you know, my sister, she's from my generation,
I mean, she's from my generation, so she's good at photography and so on.
You are good at it.
She is very good.
She gives me instructions.
She tells me to do it a little more like this.
They tell me that.
That's something that only female siblings can do.
I am already a male sibling,
It's different.
What's wrong with that? I don't know.
Don't say that.
I don't know, maybe my brother,
He probably doesn't usually take pictures.
They don't know how to take pictures,
He always takes a little blurry picture,
Or I'm half-lidded,
I always have half an eye, and the shutter timing is never right.
Oh, no.
Yes, that's right. So, I don't know,
I also read a book about being photographed,
When I turned 20,
I wanted to keep a family photo,
I wanted to leave some family photos when I turned 20, and I asked people who have always taken care of me to help me,
I rented a studio and
I rented a studio,
I rented a studio and took family photos,
And I thought it was great that they were doing it as a group,
I was really impressed.
Everyone's eyes are open.
Oh, that's right.
All the members.
That's the kind of work I do.
It doesn't fit.
Someone should definitely put on makeup.
Sounds interesting.
It is.
Why can't you open it? I was like, "Why can't I open it?
It got a little exciting.
You guys are good friends.
We're good friends.Hey~.
Lovely.
I'm a good friend,
I am saved in a big part by my family.
Yes, that's true.
Well, that concludes the first half.
How was the first half?
I'm very happy to be able to talk to you all like this,
I always see him a lot, but I don't know if he's used to me at all,
I'm hoping that you'll get used to it,
But today we were able to talk a lot on a one-on-one basis,
I was very happy.
I can look him in the eye.
We don't see eye to eye. Always.
I can't look you in the eye.
I'm doing my best now.
That's good. We still have the second half of the season.
Is that a drop?
Can I have a word with you? Just make sure he's breathing properly.
I was really worried about not being able to breathe before we started.
That's all I was worried about.
After that, I just wanted to have fun. Just breathe.
Breathe.
I was worried that I wouldn't be able to turn it around,
But you helped me a lot,
Not at all, not at all, really.
I'm looking forward to the second half.
Yes, I will. So, my partners so far are Yuki Mita of Crown Pop and Hanako Momota,
and Hanako Momota of Crown Pop.
See you tomorrow.